Viewers all over the world, say, "I am a child of God!"
By the grace of God, I am a child of God!
By the righteousness of God, I am a child of God!
You demon, I command you, in the name of Jesus -
I command you on the right, left and back -
I command you to leave my life, business, career and family!
Prayer!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Touch Your Screen By Faith And Receive
Viewers all over the world, where can you go from His presence?
Say after me:
You devil, I know you. You satan, I know you. I am a child of God.
I know you. You are a devil.
I know you. You are a killer.
I know you. You are a destroyer.
I know you. You are a thief.
I kick you out of my life!
Be kicked, in the name of Jesus!
I command you, in the name of Jesus, by the authority of the name Jesus, out!
Out!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Touch Your Screen By Faith And Receive
Viewers, wherever you are right now, satan is under your foot. You know it and I know it.
You know satan is a killer, thief, destroyer - he is under your foot.
March it right now, in the name of Jesus!
Begin to march it!
Viewers at home,
march the cause of sickness, disease, affliction, setback, disappointment and limitation.
I march you and I will continue to march you.
I march you and I will continue to walk on you.
Right now, you are under my foot; remain under my foot!
In the name of Jesus, you will remain under my foot!
In the name of Jesus, the cause of disappointment, remain under my foot!
In the name of Jesus, the cause of setback, remain under my foot!
In the name of Jesus, the cause of disease, sickness, affliction, remain under my foot!
The cause of nightmare, remain under my foot, in the name of Jesus!
Hallelujah!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Touch Your Screen By Faith And Receive
Viewers, wherever you are, whatever you are doing at this moment,
I don't know the period, the hour you are in.
Those of you under the influence of my voice right now, satan is under your foot!
I say you have silenced his voice;
his voice of sickness has been silenced;
his voice of disease has been silenced;
his voice of limitation has been silenced;
his voice of failure has been silenced.
In the name of Jesus!
I pray he remains under your foot, in Jesus' name.
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Touch Your Screen By Faith And Receive